

# **DevOps & Full Stack Web Developer**

I am a DevOps & Full Stack Web Developer. I like to solve problems and I am excited about the possibilities that technology offers to help people. I value commitment, hard work, and motivation to learn something new every day. I love teamwork and helping others. I have worked for more than ten years in highly regulated IT environments.

# Technologies & Methodologies

JavaScript PostgreSQL React JS Docker Next JS Kubernetes

Node JS AWS

Express JS Git & GitHub

HTML Agile
(S)CSS SCRUM
MongoDB ITIL

# **Education**

2020

# Full Stack Web Development Graduate

Ironhack

Learned Frontend and Backend technologies.

2002 - 2006

# Bachelor's degree, Tourism

University Carlos III of Madrid

2000 - 2002

# FP Higher Degree: Application Development

I.E.S. Ciudad Escolar

# Languages

Spanish: Native English: B2

# **Contact**

### https://ivanurra.dev

ivan.urra.dev@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/ivanurra github.com/ivanurra

# **Relevant Experience**

JUN 2023 - PRESENT REMOTE/ MADRID

# **DevOps Developer**

#### @ Philotech

- ♣ Provision of the infrastructure in a cloud environment for microservices.
- ★ Central contact person for application operation.
- → Implementation of changes and deployments.
- + Troubleshooting and analysis of logs.

AUG 2021 - JUN 2023 REMOTE

## **Full Stack Web Developer**

#### @ Secuoyas

- Write modern, performant, clean and maintainable code focused on Griddo.io, the company's own CMS, which is used by the best universities in the country.
- ✦ Work with a variety of different languages and frameworks such as JavaScript, React and Gatsby.
- ◆ Communicate and collaborate with multi-disciplinary teams of engineers, designers, and stakeholders on a daily basis.

MAR 2021 - AUG 2021 MADRID

### **Full Stack Web Developer**

# @ Auro Group

- → Built and shipped the new Auro website.
- Worked closely with designer and commercial team to develop the website using JavaScript, Vue, Nuxt and Vuetify.
- Developed and maintained code for in-house projects primarily.

MAR 2019 - MAR 2021 PALMA, ILLES BALEARS

# **IT Support Technician**

## @ Iberostar Group

- ♣ Performed high-level support to more than 50 hotels in EMEA countries.
- → Facilitated Cloud software installation and configuration in updates or openings of new hotels.
- ♣ Reduced helpdesk tickets by 60%.